Maneesh Naidu

Auckland, New Zealand. +64204826927

Visa Type: New Zealand Work Visa – Partner of a Student

maneesh.naidu@hotmail.com

https://maneeshnaidu.github.io/portfolio

OBJECTIVE

A motivated individual with in-depth knowledge of languages and development tools, seeking a position in a growth-oriented company where I can use my skills to the advantage of the company while having the scope to develop my own skills.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Software Developer/ Technical Consultant with over 5 years of experience in developing enterprise applications using mainly SAP S/4HANA, JavaScript and .NET technologies. Seeking to leverage my technical and professional expertise to grow in the field of Computer Science and Information Systems.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C#	Nodejs	Web APIs	REST
SOAP	React	SQL Server	JavaScript
HTML	CSS	npm	AWS
Azure	ASP.NET	.NET Framework	.NET Core
Bootstrap	ASP.NET Razor Pages	XML	Json
MVC	Object-oriented	Asynchronous	Functional
	Programming	Programming	Programming
Clean Architecture	MySQL	PostgreSQL	Repository Pattern
LINQ to SQL	Entity Framework Core	IIS	HTTP
	ORM		
Selenium	SAP	S/4 HANA	ABAP
SAPUI5	ABAP Test Cockpit	Visual Studio	VS Code
Eclipse IDE	GIT	GitHub	CI/CD
Agile	SCRUM	Unit Testing	

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Good oral and written communication ability.
- Self-confident, friendly, and approachable with good presentation.
- Relate well with a wide variety of people.
- Responsible and reliable.
- Thorough knowledge in the areas of Computer Science and Information Systems.
- Dynamic, creative, and enthusiastic in all things.
- Confident and strives to be the very best.
- Quick learner.
- Ability to work under pressure with minimum supervision.
- Strong leadership quality.

- Creative thinker.
- Multi-tasking and work with accuracy

WORK HISTORY

InvenioLSI

Suva 08/2021 - Present

SAP Technical Consultant

- Full stack SAP development, integration and implementation including S/4 HANA, SAPUI5, ABAP, Webdynpro, OData and BRF+ objects, SAP BTP, Node JS and Python
- Develop and implement technical specifications.
- Understand functional specifications.
- Perform unit testing.
- Support other forms of testing.
- Support functional consultants in designing solutions for the gaps identified.
- Participate in and support implementations and developments.
- Attend and participate in internal knowledge sharing sessions.
- Research new and innovative solutions in the SAP areas.

Ministry of Lands, Fiji

Suva 07/2021 – 08/2021

Systems Analyst Programmer

- Full stack web development using C#, .Net core, SQL Server and ReactJS and other technologies.
- Developing software tools to automate existing business processes prescribed by managers.
- Performing maintenance lifecycle programming for ongoing projects and software applications.
- Analyze and enhance the design and functionalities of the software systems.
- Database development and administration using MS SQL Server.
- Documentation for software developed.
- Troubleshooting software and network issues.
- Software testing, modules testing and software deployment.

Ministry of Agriculture, Fiji

Suva 04/2020 – 06/2021

Assistant Programmer/ IT Team Lead

- Full stack web development using C#, .Net core, SQL Server and ReactJS and other technologies.
- Developing software tools to automate existing business processes prescribed by managers.
- Performing maintenance lifecycle programming for ongoing projects and software applications.
- Analyze and enhance the design and functionalities of the software systems.
- Database development and administration using MS SQL Server.
- Server administration.
- Documentation for software developed.
- Troubleshooting software and network issues.
- Software testing, modules testing and software deployment.
- Provide ongoing IT support.
- Email configuration, trouble shooting.

SAAS (FIJI) LTD

Suva 01/2020 – 03/2020

Software Developer

- Full stack web development using C#, .Net core, SQL Server and ReactJS, AWS Cloud and other technologies.
- Analyze and enhance the design and functionalities of the software systems.
- Documentation for software developed.
- Provide ongoing system support.
- Troubleshooting software and network issues.
- Software testing, modules testing and software deployment.

QIT Pacific Pte Ltd

Suva

10/2019 - 12/2019

Software Developer

- Full stack web development using C#, .Net Framework, SQL Server and Backbone.js, ASP.NET Razor Pages, AWS Cloud and other technologies.
- Analyze and enhance the design and functionalities of the software systems.
- Documentation for applications developed.
- Provide ongoing system support.
- Troubleshooting software issues.
- Software testing, modules testing and software deployment.

Crimsonlogic Pte Ltd

Suva

04/2019 - 10/2019

Software Engineer

- Backend development using C#, .Net Framework, SQL Server and ASP.NET Razor Pages and Azure Cloud.
- Analyse and test the DigitalFiji system and report errors or issues and identify possible solutions.
- Analyse and enhance the design and functionalities of the software systems.
- Writing SQL scripts for data patches in the backend which can't be done through system functionalities.
- Provide user training on the new systems built Birth Death Marriage (BDM) System and Register of Companies (ROC).
- Prepare system documentation and Standard Operating Procedures (SOPs) slides and diagrams for DigitalFiji modules.
- Provide ongoing system support.
- Troubleshooting software and network issues.
- Software testing, payment modules testing and software deployment.
- Automation testing using MAVEN and Selenium

Fijian Competition & Consumer Commission

Suva

01/2019 - 03/2019

IT Intern

- Provide ongoing IT support.
- Email configuration, trouble shooting.
- Develop Web pages as per IT officer's/ Management's Requirements

QUALIFICATIONS

Fiji National University

Suva 2016 - 2018

Bachelor of Science

Computer Science and Information Systems

ACHIEVEMENTS

- APO Digital Government Transformation Training Ministry of Agriculture Representative
- Runner Up of Smart City Challenge Suva Hackathon 2018 Team leader of Fiji National University Team

INTERESTS

 Full marathon runner, enjoy playing futsal. Have represented Fijian youth and district football teams.

REFEREES

Belinda Bithell

Senior Project Manager InvenioLSI +679 782 4872 belinda.bithell@inveniolsi.com

Nitin Buantoa

Vice President – Delivery & Account Management InvenioLSI +679 940 3290 nitin.buantoa@inveniolsi.com Francis Gomas
Web Engineer
ANZ Fiji
+61 406963065
francisgomes721@gmail.com